<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Articles</title><link href="http://articles.0atman.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://articles.0atman.com/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://articles.0atman.com/</id><updated>2014-12-16T10:20:00+00:00</updated><entry><title>Cory Doctorow, on hearing aids</title><link href="http://articles.0atman.com/cory-doctorow-on-hearing-aids.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-12-16T10:20:00+00:00</updated><author><name>0atman</name></author><id>tag:articles.0atman.com,2014-12-16:cory-doctorow-on-hearing-aids.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you’re my age and grew up with the Walkman or you’re little younger and you grow up with the iPod, you will have logged enough punishing earbud hours that by the time you reach a certain age you will almost certainly need a hearing aid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is vanishingly unlikely that that hearing aid will be a retro, beige, hipster, analog transistor hearing aid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead it will be a computer that you put in your body and, depending on how it works, it can:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;make you hear things that aren’t there&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;make you not hear things that are there&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tell other people what you’ve heard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’ve got to get this right&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Everything Is Broken</title><link href="http://articles.0atman.com/everything-is-broken.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-05-29T10:20:00+01:00</updated><author><name>0atman</name></author><id>tag:articles.0atman.com,2014-05-29:everything-is-broken.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"There’s your choice: constantly risk clicking on dangerous malware, or live under an overpass, leaving notes on the lawn of your former house telling your children you love them and miss them.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://medium.com/message/everything-is-broken-81e5f33a24e1"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Adam Savage’s Ten Rules for Success</title><link href="http://articles.0atman.com/adam-savages-ten-rules-for-success.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-04-06T10:20:00+01:00</updated><author><name>0atman</name></author><id>tag:articles.0atman.com,2014-04-06:adam-savages-ten-rules-for-success.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get good at something. Really good. Get good at as many things as you can. Being good at one thing makes it easier to get good at other things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting good at stuff takes practice. Lots and lots of practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get OBSESSED. Everyone at the top of their field is obsessed with what they’re doing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doing something well and thoroughly is its OWN reward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Show and Tell. If you do something well and you’re happy with it, for FSM’s sake, tell EVERYONE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want something, ASK. If something piques your interest, tell someone. If you want to learn something, ask someone, like your BOSS. As an employer, I can tell you, people who want to learn new skills are people I want to keep employed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have GOALS. Make up goals. Set goals. Regularly assess where you are and where you want to be in terms of them. This is a kind of prayer that works, and works well. Allow for the fact that things will NEVER turn out like you think they will, and you must be prepared to end up miles from where you intended.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be nice. To EVERYONE. Life is way too short to be an asshole. If you are an asshole, apologize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FAIL. You will fail. It’s one of our jobs in life. Keep failing. When you fail, admit it. When you don’t, don’t get cocky. ‘Cause you’re just about to fail again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WORK YOUR ASS OFF. Work like your life depends on it…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://boingboing.net/2013/08/19/adam-savages-ten-rules-for-s.html"&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="mythbusters"></category><category term="makers"></category><category term="done"></category></entry><entry><title>An open letter to moonpig.com</title><link href="http://articles.0atman.com/an-open-letter-to-moonpigcom.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-01-05T10:20:00+00:00</updated><author><name>0atman</name></author><id>tag:articles.0atman.com,2014-01-05:an-open-letter-to-moonpigcom.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;It was with much distress that I read this article about your insecure API: http://ifc0nfig.com/moonpig-vulnerability/&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The author, Paul Price, showed that you do not use any authentication. I have tested this myself (I am a software engineer, and it was TRIVIAL) and can confirm the flagrant disregard for my privacy in your service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to him, you have had at least SEVENTEEN MONTHS to fix this, and not done so. That is unacceptable!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, happily for you, the solution is simple: As Paul says in his article, you do have OAuth enabled already. Please start using it across all clients and disable the old insecure API at /rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that this information is public, you have very little time before your customer’s details are leaked online if it has not already. It will be very clear that the blame will not be in the crackers who took the data, but you, who not only left the door unlocked, but decided not to build the house in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>